Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs WAG.257
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies
  - In the Counting House, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - In the Jungle of Cities, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - In the Summer House, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Inadmissible Evidence, undated (Box 22, Folder 9A)
  - Incident at Vichy, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Independence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Indian Wants the Bronx, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Indians, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Indulgences in the Louisville Harem, Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Inherit the Wind, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Innocents, Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Inside U.S.A., Undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Inspecting Carol, Undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Inspector Calls, Undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Inspector General, Undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts (IASTA), Undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Into the Woods, Undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Iolanthe, Undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Iphigenia in Aulis, Undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Irene, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Irma La Douce, Undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Is There Life After High School, Undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Isn't It Romantic, Undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - It's a Bird, It's a Plane, It's Superman, Undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - It's So Nice to be Civilized, Undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Ivanov, Undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - J, Undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - J, 1920s (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - J, 1930s (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - J, 1940s (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - J, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - J, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - J, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - J, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - J, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - J, 2000s (Box 22, Folder 40A)
  - Jackie Mason's The World According to Me!, Brand New, Politically Incorrect, Undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Jacobowsky and the Colonel, Undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Jacques Brel is alive and well and living in Paris, Undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Jake's Women, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jamaica, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - James Joyce's Dubliners and Women, Undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jane Eyre, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Janie, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - JB, Undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jealousy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Jeeves Takes Charge, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jeffry, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jekyll and Hyde, Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Jelly's Last Jam, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Jerome Robbins' Ballet: U.S.A. and Broadway, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Jerry's Girls, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12A)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Jimmy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Jitney, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Joan of Lorraine, Undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Joe Egg, Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, Undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - John and Jen, Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - John Brown's Body, Undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - John Bull's Other Island, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - John Gabriel Borkman, Undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Johnny Johnson, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Johnny No-Trump, Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Journey of the Fifth Horse, Undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jubilee, Undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jubilee! A Theatre Festival Celebrating the Black Experience, Undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Judgment at Nuremberg, Undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Julius Caesar, Undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jumpers, Undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - June Moon, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Junior Miss, Undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Juno and the Paycock, Undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - K, Undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - K, 1920s (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - K, 1930s (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - K, 1940s (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - K, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - K, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - K, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - K, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - K, 1990s (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - K, 2000s (Box 23, Folder 43A)
  - K2, Undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Kean, Undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Keely and Du, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy's Children, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky Cycle, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Key Exchange, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Key Largo, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Keystone, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5A)
  - Killing of Sister George, Undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Kind Lady, Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Kind Sir, Undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Kindertransport, Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - King and I, Undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - King Hedley, Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - King John, Undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - King Lear, Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - King of Hearts, Undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - King of the Schnorrers, Undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Kingdom of Earth, Undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Kismet, Undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Kiss and Tell, Undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Kiss Me Kate, Undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Kiss Me Quick Before the Lava Reaches the Village, Undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman, Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Kitchen, Undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Knack, Undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Knickerbocker Holiday, Undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Krapp's Last Tape, Undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Kurt Weill Cabaret, Undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - L, Undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - L, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - L, 1920s (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - L, 1930s (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - L (file 1 of 2), 1940s (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - L (file 2 of 2), 1940s (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - L, 1950s (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - L (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - L (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - L (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - L (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - L (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - L (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - L, 1990s (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - L, 2000s (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - La Bete, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - La Cage aux folles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - La Plume de Ma Tante, Undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - La Ronde, Undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - La Strada, Undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ladies in Retirement, Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Lady Be Good, Undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lady Day at Emerson's Bar and Grill, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Lady from the Sea, Undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lady in Question, Undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Lady in the Dark, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lady Windermere's Fan, Undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Ladyhouse Blues, Undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Lady's not for Burning, Undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Landscape and Silence, Undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Landscape of the Body, Undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Lark, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Last Minstrel Show, Undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Last of Mrs. Cheyney, Undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Last of Mrs. Lincoln, Undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Last of the Marx Brothers' Writers, Undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, Undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Last Summer at Bluefish Cove, Undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Late George Apley, Undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Later Life, Undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Laughing Wild, Undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Laura, Undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Leader of the Pack, Undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Learned Ladies, Undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Leave it to Jane, Undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Leave it to Me!, Undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Legend of Lovers, Undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Legends, Undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Legs Diamond, Undated (Box 25, Folder 40A)
  - Lemon Sky, Undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Lend an Ear, Undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lend Me a Tenor, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Lenny, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Les Liaisons Dangereuses, Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Les Misérables, Undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Lesson(and with The Chairs), Undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Lesson from Aloes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Let Me Hear You Smile, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Let My People Come, Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Let's Face It, Undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Let's Get a Divorce, Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Letter, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Lettice and Lovage, Undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Libel, Undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Lie of the Mind, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Life, Undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Life and Adventures of Nicholas Nickelby, Undated (Box 26, Folder 17A)
  - Life and Limb, Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Life in the Theatre, Undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Liver with Father, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Life with Mother, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Light Up the Sky, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Like Father-Like Son, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Li'L Abner, Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Liliom, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Line, Undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Lion in Winter, Undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Lips Together, Teeth Apart, Undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Lisbon Traviata, Undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Little Black Book, Undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Little Boxes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Little Foxes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Little Johnny Jones, Undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Little Mary Sunshine, Undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Little Me, Undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Little Murders, Undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Little Night Music, Undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Little Shop of Horrors, Undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Live Like Pigs, Undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Living at Home, Undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Living Room, Undated (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Living Theatre, Undated (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Local Stigmatic, Undated (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Lock Up Your Daughters, Undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Lolita/Lolita My Love, Undated (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Loman Family Picnic, Undated (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Lone Star(and with Pvt. Wars), Undated (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Lonely Planet, Undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Long Christmas Dinner, Undated (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night, Undated (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Long Wharf Theatre, Undated (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Look Back in Anger, Undated (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Look Homeward, Angel, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Look: We've Come Through, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Loose Ends, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Loot, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Lorelei, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Loss of Roses, Undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lost in the Stars, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Lost in Yonkers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Louisiana Purchase, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Love and Kisses, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Love from a Stranger, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Love is a Time of Day, Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Love Letters, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Love of Four Colonels, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Love Rides the Rails, Undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Love! Valour! Compassion!, Undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Lovely Light, Undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Lovely Sunday for Creve Coeur, Undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Lovers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Lovers and Other Strangers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Love's Labour's Lost, Undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Lower Depths, Undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Lulu, Undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Lunch Hour, Undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Lute Song, Undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Luther, Undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Luv, Undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Lysistrata, Undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - M, Undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - M, 1910s (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - M (file 1 of 2), 1920s (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - M (file 2 of 2), 1920s (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - M, 1930s (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - M (file 1 of 2), 1940s (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - M (file 2 of 2), 1940s (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - M (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - M (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - M (file 1 of 4), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - M (file 2 of 4), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - M (file 3 of 4), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - M (file 4 of 4), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - M (file 1 of 3), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - M (file 2 of 3), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - M (file 3 of 3), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - M (file 1 of 3), 1980s (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - M (file 2 of 3), 1980s (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - M (file 3 of 3), 1980s (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - M (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - M (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - M, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - M. Butterfly, Undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Macbeth, Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Machinal, Undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Mack and Mabel, Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Mad forest, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Madwoman of Central Park West, Undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Madwoman of Chaillot, Undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Mahalia, Mahalia's Song, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Maggie Flynn, Undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Magic Show, Undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Magnificent Yankee, Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Maid in the Ozarks, Undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Maids, Undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Mail, Undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Major Barbara, Undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Majority of One, Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Makropoulos Secret, Undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Male Animal, Undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Mamba's Daughters, Undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Mame, Undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Man and Superman, Undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Man for All Seasons, Undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Man in the Glass Booth, Undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Man of Destiny, Undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Man of La Mancha, Undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Man With a Load of Mischief, Undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Man With the Flower in His Mouth, Undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Man Who Came to Dinner, Undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Man's a Man, Undated (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Marathon (s) at Ensemble Studio Theatre, Undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - March of the Falsettos, Undated (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Marco Polo Sings a Solo, Undated (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Mark Twain Tonight, Undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Marriage-Go-Round, Undated (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Marriage of Bette and Boo, Undated (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Marriage of Figaro, Undated (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Marriage of Mr. Mississippi, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Marry Me a Little, Undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Marvin's Room, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Mary, Mary, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Mary Rose, Undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Mary Stuart, Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Mass Appeal, Undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Master Builder, Undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Master Class, Undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Master Harold and the Boys, Undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Mata Hari, Undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Matchmaker, Undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - McCarter Theatre, Undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Me and Juliet, Undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Me and My Girl, Undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Me and Thee, Undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Me Nobody Knows, Undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Measure for Measure, Undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Medal of Honor Rag, Undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Medea, Undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Meet Me in St. Louis, Undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Member of the Wedding, Undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Merchant of Venice, Undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Merlin, Undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Merrily We Roll Along, Undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Merry Widow, Undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor, Undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Metamorphoses, Undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Middle Ages, Undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Midnight Ride of Alvin Blum, Undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Midsummer Nights' Dream, Undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Mighty Gents, Undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Mikado, Undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Milk and Honey, Undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Milk Train Doesn't Stop Here Anymore, Undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Milliken Breakfast Shows, 1974-1977 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Minnesota Theatre Company, Undated (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Miracle Worker, Undated (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Mirror Repertory Company, Mirror Theatre, Undated (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Misalliance, Undated (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Misanthrope, Undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Miser, Undated (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Miss Ever's Boys, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Miss Firecracker Contest, Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Miss Margarida's Way, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Miss Saigon, Undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Missouri Repertory Theatre, Undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Moby Dick, Undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Modigliani, Undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Molly, Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Monday After the Miracle, Undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Money, Undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Month in the Country, Undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Montserrat, Undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Moon for the Misbegotten, Undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Moon Over Buffalo, Undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Moonchildren, Undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - More Stately Mansions, Undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Morning Star, Undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Morning's at Seven, Undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Most Happy Fella, Undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Mother Courage, Undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Mother of Us All, Undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Mound Builders, Undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Mourning Becomes Electra, Undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Mousetrap, Undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Mrs. Klein, Undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Mrs. McThing, Undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession, Undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, Undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Murder Among Friends, Undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Murder at the Vicarage, Undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Murder in the Cathedral, Undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Murder is Announced, Undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Music Box Revue(Irving Berlin), Undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Music Man, Undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Musical Comedy Murders, Undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - My Children, My Africa, Undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - My Fair Lady, Undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - My Fat Friend, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - My One and Only, Undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - My Sister Eileen, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - My Sweet Charlie, Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - My Three Angels, Undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - My Wife and I, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - My X-Rated Daughter/My Daughter's Rated X, Undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Mystery of Edwin Drood, Undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Mystery of Irma Vep, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - N, Undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - N, 1920s (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - N, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - N, 1940s (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - N, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - N, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - N (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - N (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - N (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - N (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - N, 1990s (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - N, 2000s (Box 32, Folder 20A)
  - Naomi Court, Undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Narrow Road to the Deep North, Undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Natalie Needs a Nightie, Undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - National Health, Undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - National Players, Undated (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - National Repertory Theatre, Undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Native Son, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Naughty Marietta, Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Neddy, Undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Negro Ensemble Company (Repertory), Undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Playhouse School of the Theatre, Undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Nerd, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Never Too Late, Undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - New Faces, Undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - New Mexican Rainbow Fishing, Undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - New Moon, Undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival (Repertory), Undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - New Yorkers, Undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Next Wave Festival, Undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Nice Place to Visit, Undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Nick and Nora, Undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Night is Mother to the Day, Undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - 'night Mother, Undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Night of January 16th, Undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Night of the Iguana, Undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Night of the Tribades, Undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Night Thoreau Spent in Jail, Undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Night Watch, Undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Nightclub Cantata, Undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Nine, Undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Nite Club Confidential, Undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - No Exit, Undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - No-Frills Revue, Undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - No Hard Feelings, Undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - No, No, Nanette, Undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - No Place to Be Somebody, Undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - No Sex Please, We're British, Undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - No Strings, Undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - No Time for Sergeants, Undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Nobody Loves an Albatross, Undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Noel Coward in Two Keys, Noel Coward's Sweet Potato, Noel and Gertie, Undated (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Noises Off, Undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Normal Heart, Undated (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Norman Conquests, Undated (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Norman, Is That You?, Undated (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Not for Children, Undated (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Not in the Book, Undated (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Now I Lay Me Down to Sleep, Undated (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Nude with Violin, Undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Nunsense, Nunsense II, Nunsense Story, Undated (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Nutcracker: A Play, Nutcracker: A Musical Play, Undated (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Nuts, Undated (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - O, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - O, 1910s (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - O, 1920s (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - O, 1930s (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - O, 1940s (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - O, 1950s (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - O, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - O, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - O, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - O, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - O Mistress Mine, Undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Octette Bridge Club, Undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Odd Couple, Undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Odd Man In, Undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Oedipus includes Oedipus Rex and Oedipus at Colonus, Undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Of Mice and Men, Undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Of the Fields, Lately, Undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Of Thee I Sing, Undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Oh, Boy, Undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Oh! Calcutta!, Undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Oh Captain!, Undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Oh Coward!, Undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Oh, Kay!, Undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Oh What a Lovely War, Undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Oil City Symphony, Undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Oklahoma, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 1)
  - Old Acquaintance, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 2)
  - Old Globe, San Diego, California, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 3)
  - Old Lady's Guide to Survival, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 4)
  - Old Times, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 5)
  - Old World, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 6)
  - Oleanna, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 7)